const QUESTIONS = [
    {
        question: 'What premier league team won 13 premier league titles?',
        answers: [ 
            'Manchester City',
            'Arsenal',
            'Chelsea',
            'Manchester United'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Manchester United',
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the most expensive transfer in the world?',
        answers: [
            'Neymar Jr.',
            'Eden Hazard',
            'Paul Pogba',
            'Kylian Mbappe'
        ], 
        correctAnswer: 'Neymar jr.',
    },
    {
        question: 'What year did Spain win their first FIFA World Cup?',
        answers: [
            '1998',
            '2010',
            '2002',
            '2018'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '2010',
    },
    {
        question: 'Who Infamously Scored a goal with their hands and called it the \"The Hand of God\"?',
        answers: [
            'Lionel Messi',
            'Diego Maradona',
            'Ronaldo (Brazil)',
            'Franz Beckenbauer'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Diego Maradona',
    },
    {
        question: 'How many ballon d\'ors does Lionel Messi have?',
        answers: [
            '4',
            '6',
            '3',
            '5'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '5',
    },
    {
        question: 'What were the two teams that played in the Champions League Final in 2006?',
        answers: [
            'Milan v. Liverpool',
            'Real Madrid v. Juventus',
            'Barcelona v. Arsenal',
            'Porto v. Monaco'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Barcelona v. Arsenal',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which Nation does Eden Harzard play for?',
        answers: [
            'France',
            'Netherlands',
            'Germany',
            'Belgium'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Belgium'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is current Manager of Newcastle United?',
        answers: [
            'Rafa Benitez',
            'Jose Mourinho',
            'Pep Guardiola',
            'Eddie Howe'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Rafa Benitez',
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the the nickname of Leicester City F.C.?',
        answers: [
            'Reds',
            'Foxes',
            'Wolves',
            'The Swans'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Foxes',
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the top Scorer in Champions League history?',
        answers: [
            'Sammuel Eto\'o',
            'Mo Salah',
            'Cristiano Ronaldo',
            'Antoine Griezmann'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Cristiano Ronaldo',
    },
]
